Tufts Community Union (TCU) Senate Records UA094
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Community Union (TCU) Senate Records
1962 -- 2015
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Community Union
Tufts Community Union Senate
UA094
6.37 Linear Feet 3 record cartons, 1 document box, and 1 oversize box
This collection contains the records of the Tufts Community Union (TCU) Senate, the student undergraduate legislative/executive body.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into two series: TCU Senate records and 2020 accessions.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains records of the Tufts Community Union (TCU) Senate. Materials include agendas, meeting minutes, reports, publications, manuals, anonymous course evaluations, clippings, and a student survey. Records date from 1962-2015.
Biographical / Historical
Established in 1968, the Tufts Community Union (TCU) Senate is the student parliament and legislative/executive body of TCU Student Government for the undergraduate students of the College of Liberal Arts and Jackson College and the College of Engineering. As of Spring 2000, it is charged with representing the needs and interests of the TCU before the faculty of the undergraduate colleges, the administration, and the Trustees of Tufts College. Through the Treasury, it oversees the use of the student activities fee and ensures that the needs and interests of the students are voiced.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by the TCU Senate, 2012-2019.
Student life; Student Activities -- Student Government, Clubs, and Organizations; Student activism; Student life; Tufts Community Union; Tufts Community Union Senate
- TCU Senate records, 1967 -- 2012; UA094.000065; 0.5 Linear Feet 1 document box
  Conditions Governing Access
  This series is open for research.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains anonymous course evaluations compiled for student use, as well as reports, manuals, and publications produced by the Tufts Community Union (TCU) Senate.
  Arrangement
  Material was maintained in received order.
  - Course evaluations, 1967 -- 1988; UA094.000058; 5 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 1-5)
    Open for research.
  - Senate reports, 1984 -- 1985; UA094.000059; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Retreat manual, 1998 -- 2000; UA094.000060; 2 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 7-8)
  - Report on overcrowding, 1978-12-18; UA094.000061; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - The Ivory Book, 2011 -- 2012; UA094.000062; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - State of the Senate, 1990-01-12; UA094.000063; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Treasury procedures manual, 1999 -- 2000; UA094.000064; 1 Folder(s) (Box 5, Folder 12)
- 2020 accessions, 1962 -- 2015; circa 1981 -- 2015; UA094.000010; 5.87 Linear Feet 3 record cartons and 1 oversize box
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  This series contains records of Tufts Community Union (TCU) Senate. Included are log books, consisting of agendas, minutes, and supplementary materials for TCU meetings; records such as publications, manuals, and project forms; project books consisting of project reports; State of the Senate reports; newspaper clippings; and a student survey. Materials date from 1962 to 2015, with the bulk of materials dating from 1981-2015.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Transferred by the TCU Senate, 2012-2019, accession UA-2020-029.
  - TCU Senate records, 1962 -- 1981; UA094.000011; 2 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - TCU Senate project book, 1982 -- 1994; UA094.000012; 2 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 3-6)
  - TCU Senate project book, 1982 -- 1995; UA094.000013; 2 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 7-10)
  - TCU Senate project book, 1983 -- 1986; UA094.000014; 2 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 11-14)
  - State of the Senate report, 1984 December 31; UA094.000015; 2 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - State of the Senate report, 1985 January 20; UA094.000016; 2 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - State of the Senate report, 1985 April 8; UA094.000017; 2 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - TCU Senate records, 1985 -- 1999; UA094.000018; 2 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 18-20)
  - State of the Senate report, 1987 January 25; UA094.000019; 2 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - State of the Senate report, 1987 September 8; UA094.000020; 2 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - TCU Senate logbook, 1989 -- 1992; UA094.000021; 2 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 23-24)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences FY budget, 1990 -- 1991; UA094.000022; 2 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Resident Student survey, 1990; UA094.000023; 2 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 26-27)
  - State of the Senate report, 1990 January 21; UA094.000024; 2 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Arts and Sciences Library report, 1991 February 28; UA094.000025; 2 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - TCU Senate logbook, 1992 -- 1994; UA094.000026; 2 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 30-32)
  - TCU Senate records, 1993 -- 1994; UA094.000027; 2 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 1-3)
  - State of the Senate report, 1994 September 18; UA094.000028; 2 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - TCU Senate Retreat manual, 1994; UA094.000029; 2 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - TCU Senate records, 1994 -- 1995; UA094.000030; 2 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 6-9)
  - TCU Senate records, 1994 -- 1996; UA094.000031; 2 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 10-12)
  - Hotung Café, circa 1995-2000; UA094.000032; 2 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - TCU Senate logbook, 1995 -- 1996; UA094.000033; 2 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - TCU Senate records, 1996 -- 2001; UA094.000034; 2 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - TCU Senate records, 1997 -- 1998; UA094.000035; 2 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 16-17)
  - TCU Senate records, 1999 -- 2000; UA094.000036; 2 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - TCU Senate Retreat manual, 1999 -- 2000; UA094.000037; 2 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Brochures, circa 2000-2012; UA094.000038; 2 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - TCU Senate records part 1, 2001 -- 2002; UA094.000039; 2 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 21-24)
  - TCU Senate records part 2, 2001 -- 2002; UA094.000040; 2 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 25-28)
  - Faculty Appointments report, 2002; UA094.000041; 2 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - TCU Education Committee, 2002 -- 2003; UA094.000042; 2 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
  - TCU Senate records, 2002 -- 2003; UA094.000043; 2 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 3-6)
  - Andrew Caplan TCU Senate records, 2003 -- 2004; UA094.000044; 2 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - TCU Senate logbook, 2003 -- 2004; UA094.000045; 2 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 8-12)
  - TCU Senate logbook, 2004 -- 2005; UA094.000046; 2 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 13-14)
  - TCU Senate logbook, 2005 -- 2006; UA094.000047; 2 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 15-18)
  - Callie Kolbe TCU Senate records, 2006 -- 2007; UA094.000048; 2 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 19-20)
  - TCU Senate Success Kit, 2007 -- 2008; UA094.000049; 2 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 21-22)
  - Antonella Scarano TCU Senate records, 2008 -- 2009; UA094.000050; 2 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 23-24)
  - Press book, 2008 -- 2009; UA094.000057; 1 Items (Box 4)
  - Antonella Scarano TCU Senate records, 2009 -- 2010; UA094.000051; 2 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 25-26)
  - TCU Senate records, 2009 -- 2015; UA094.000052; 2 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Office for Campus Life, 2012 -- 2013; UA094.000053; 2 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Student Judicial Process manual, 2012 -- 2013; UA094.000054; 2 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Tufts Internship profiles, 2012; UA094.000055; 2 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - TCU Senate records, 2014 -- 2015; UA094.000056; 2 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 31-32)